Id;Default;en;de
CheckOverwriteTitel;Save as...;Save as...;Speichern unter...
CheckOverwriteMessage;The file already exists. Do you want to overwrite the file? ;The file already exists. Do you want to overwrite the file? ;Die Datei ist bereits vorhanden. Möchten Sie die Datei überschreiben?
CheckOverwriteBusy;Another client is saving a recipe at the moment. This action is canceled. ;Another client is saving a recipe at the moment. This action is canceled. ;Ein anderer Client speichert gerade eine Rezeptur. Diese Aktion wird abgebrochen.
;;;
